what's going on guys Josh pook here and
大家好，我是Josh Pook。
in today's video we are going to be
在今天的视频中，我们将
taking a look at the all-in-one desktop
了解一下这款集桌面
and Docker AI application with built-in
和Docker功能于一体的AI应用程序，它内置了
rag AI agents and more this tool is
Rag AI代理等功能。这款工具
extremely easy to set up I'm going to
设置起来非常简单，我将在
show you how you can do it in the next 5
接下来的5分钟内向您展示如何操作。
minutes this is anything llm you can
这就是Anything LLM，您可以将
configure it to use AI agents with
其配置为使用
pretty much any model and you can use it
几乎任何模型的AI代理，还可以用它来
to chat with your documents do local reg
处理文档、进行本地注册（使用您
with your own private data that isn't
不共享的私有数据），
shared and then you can create AI agents
然后您可以创建AI代理
and give them access to tools like web
并赋予它们访问网络
searching web scraping generating charts
搜索、网页抓取、生成图表等工具的权限。
and much more let's dive right into
让我们马上开始吧！
it all right guys so all the links will
所有链接都将在
be linked down below including the link
下方，包括
to the GitHub repo right here as well as
GitHub代码库的链接以及
the link to the official anything llm
Anything LLM官方
website right so some of the features of
网站的链接。Anything LLM的一些功能
anything llm includes a oneclick
包括一键
installation so it's very very simple
安装，非常简单。
you can literally click download
您只需点击“下载
anything llm right here and it will
Anything LLM”即可，它就会
start downloading onto your system we'll
开始下载到您的系统中。我们马上就来演示一下。
do that in just a second um fully
完全
private like I mentioned before so so it
私密。 就像我之前提到的，它
can run fully on your device without any
无需网络连接即可在您的设备上完全运行。
right it supports so many different
它支持很多不同的
models so many different you know closed
模型，包括闭
Source models open source models olama
源模型、开源模型等等，比如 Olama、
LM Studio you name it it is within
LM Studio 等等，几乎涵盖了
anything llm all right and you can
Anything LLM。您可以
upload many different documents from
上传各种文档，例如
PDFs txts MDS markdown files really you
PDF、TXT、MDS、Markdown 文件等等，
know almost anything you can think of in
几乎任何您能想到的
a file format you can upload to anything
文件格式都可以上传到 Anything
llm and use it within your local rag all
LLM，并在您的本地环境中使用。
right and they say batteries included so
他们说
anything llm comes with a locally
Anything LLM 是“开箱即用”，它自带本地
running default for your llm embedder
运行的默认 LLM 嵌入器
and storage for full privacy out of box
和存储空间，开箱即用，完全保护您的隐私。
so they have their own embedder as well
他们有自己的嵌入器
as Vector store that is 100% private all
以及 100% 私密的 Vector Store。
right so first things first is we're
首先，我们
going to click on download anything llm
点击“下载 Anything LLM”，
and then you can select of course your
然后选择您的
different operating system whether
操作系统，无论
that's Mac uh windows or l and then
是 Mac、Windows 还是其他操作系统，
actually download it and install it onto
下载并安装到
your system all right you could also
您的系统上。您也可以
self-host it and deploy it on you know
自行托管并将其部署到
these different Services Docker AWS
各种服务上，例如 Docker、AWS、
digital ocean render gcp Railway a bunch
Digital Ocean、Render、GCP、Railway
more but you know the simplest way that
等等。最简单的方法是……
I found is to simply just download the
我找到的方法就是直接下载
installer okay now once you actually
安装程序。
install anything llm you can open it on
安装好 LLM 后，你可以在桌面上打开它。第一次
actually open it for the first time it
打开时，它
will walk you through you know selecting
会引导你选择
your default llm M you know you'll have
默认的 LLM 模块。你会看到
multiple different llm providers to
多个不同的 LLM 提供商可供
select from so if I go here go to let's
选择。我点击这里，
just check out our instant settings so
看看我们的即时设置，
it will kind of look like this you'll
它看起来大概是这样的：你会
see the llm providers you can select
看到 LLM 提供商，你可以选择
anything llm open AI Azure anthropic
OpenAI、Azure、Athropologie、
Gemini hugging face olama LM Studio
Gemini、Hugging Face、Olama、LM Studio、
local AI together AI fireworks mistal
LocalAI、TogetherAI、Fireworks、Mistal、
perplexity open router Gro all right you
Perplexity、OpenRouter、Gro 等等。好了，你们
get the point guys you can see so many
明白我的意思了。你会看到很多
different ones from Deep seek X Ai and
不同的 LLM，比如 DeepSeek X AI。
then you can you know if it's API key is
如果需要 API 密钥，
required you can enter that in and then
你可以输入密钥，然后
select the specific model so we got for
选择特定的模型。我们这里以
open AI we have pretty much all the
OpenAI 为例，它几乎包含了所有
different models you can see here if I
不同的模型。如果我
go here and go to olama you'll see that
点击这里，选择 Olama，你会看到
it automatically has the AMA base URL
它自动显示了 AMA 基本 URL。
right here if you need to change that
如果你需要更改它，
for whatever reason you could you can
你可以
change some of the advanced settings
修改一些高级设置。
here and then you'll see the different
这里是设置，然后你会看到不同的
ol models right here so um these are
OLA 模型，嗯，这些
just the ones I have right now so like
只是我现在拥有的模型，比如
quen 22 we got llama
Queen 22，我们有 Llama
3.1 and if you don't know how to um set
3.1。如果你不知道如何
up AMA you can simply just go to ama.com
设置 AMA，你可以直接访问 ama.com，
and then make sure you download olama
确保下载 AMA，然后
and then um you can just literally click
点击
on download AMA and then go to models
下载 AMA，再进入模型
right here and find a specific model you
页面，找到你
want like llama 3.2 and then just run
想要的特定模型，比如 Llama 3.2。安装好 AMA 后，
this command in your terminal once you
在终端运行这个命令，就可以
then that will download the model right
下载模型了。LM
the same thing with LM Studio you can do
Studio 的操作也一样，
that or really any of these different
或者其他任何软件都可以。
ones so you can use local models with
你可以使用本地模型，
this which is really nice or you could
这很棒，也可以
use closed Source models so either one
使用闭源模型。两种
works I'm just going to keep it with
方法都行。为了
open AI here just to make sure
保证视频演示快速，这里我只用 OpenAI，
but you can definitely use this with uh
但你当然也可以使用
like I said local open- Source models as
本地开源模型。
well I will also ask you on the next
下一页我会问你
page I believe for the vector database
关于矢量数据库的问题，
and then better I I can't remember if it
还有更好的方法。 我记不清
exactly shows that on the setup page you
设置页面上是否明确显示了这一点，但你
can literally just go through the setup
可以直接浏览设置
page it really doesn't matter necessar
页面，其实
necessarily what you choose for that um
你选择什么并不重要。嗯，
I believe it will ask you to create a
我相信它会要求你创建一个
workspace because all those settings
工作区，因为
that you pick you can change afterwards
你选择的所有设置之后都可以更改。
so um that's what I'm showing you right
嗯，这就是我现在要演示的内容。LLM
now so there's really two areas of
实际上包含两个区域，
anything llm this is like kind of the
这有点像
chat interface you know the the
聊天界面，你知道，它的
interface that looks similar to
界面看起来类似于
something like chat GPT where we have
GPT 聊天，
over here on the left we have our
左侧是我们的
workspaces so for example a workspace is
工作区，例如，一个工作区在
right here another workspace is right
这里，另一个工作区在
here and then we have our chats
这里，然后是
basically within that workspace so these
工作区内的聊天，这些聊天被
are called threads and basically you can
称为“线程”。基本上，你可以
configure settings individually for each
为每个工作区单独配置设置。
workspace so like here's the general
例如，这里是常规
settings where we can change our name we
设置，我们可以在这里更改名称，
could delete a workspace we could change
可以删除工作区，可以更改
the chat settings for this specific
特定
workspace so right here it um you could
工作区的聊天设置。这里，你可以
use the system default and this will use
使用系统默认值，这将使用
the system llm preferences for this
系统 LLM 首选项作为此
workspace so that's I'll show you that's
工作区的首选项。我会向你展示这个，就像
like the one that you set up at the
你一
start or you can change this as well you
开始设置的一样，你也可以更改它。
can change the system default and I'll
更改系统默认设置，我马上就给
like I'll show you how to get there in
你演示一下怎么操作。
just a second um but yeah you could also
嗯，你也可以
really pick any specific llm here so you
选择任何特定的语言学习模型（LLM），这样你就
could have different workspaces with
可以根据需要设置不同的工作区和
different llm set up if need be so you
不同的LLM。比如，你
could have like your local workspace
可以设置本地工作区、
your open AI workspace your anthropic
OpenAI工作区、Athropologie工作区等等。
options here like uh chat uh chat mode
这里还有一些不同的选项，比如聊天、聊天模式（
so you can do chat query um chat history
你可以进行聊天查询、查看聊天记录）、
right here prompts so basic prompt query
提示（基本提示、查询
mode refusal prompt LL
模式、拒绝提示、LL
temperature and you can read the
温度等等）。
descriptions here in case you're
如果你
wondering what each one of these are you
想知道每个选项的具体功能，可以查看这里的说明。你也
can simply update workspace all right
可以直接更新工作区。好了，
and then here we have our Vector
这里是我们的向量
database so we can see U all the
数据库，我们可以看到所有
different settings here we can see the
不同的设置。我们可以看到
max Contex Snippets we can see the
最大上下文片段数，可以看到
document similarity threshold right here
文档相似度阈值（低、
from low medium high no and you could
中、高、无）。你可以
reset Vector database and then we also
重置向量数据库。此外，我们还有
have agent configuration so you'll see
代理配置。你会看到，在
here you can do the same thing you could
这里你可以进行相同的操作：你可以为
specific llm for the agent side of
代理选择特定的代理或特定的LLM。
things and I'll show you how you can use
我马上就给你演示如何使用
agents in just just a second now if you
代理。 其次，如果您
click on configure agent skills this
点击“配置代理技能”，这
will actually take you to like your
将带您进入
anything llm instant settings so this is
Anything LLM 的即时设置页面。在这里，
like where you can change your default
您可以更改默认设置，
like I was showing you before your
就像我之前向您展示的那样，您的
default llm which right now rs's open AI
默认 LLM 数据库（目前是 RS 的 OpenAI）。
you can change your default Vector
您可以更改默认的 Vector
database all right so by default it's uh
数据库。默认情况下，它
on Lance DB this is 100% local V Vector
使用 LanceDB，这是一个 100% 本地的 Vector
DB that runs on the same instance of
数据库，运行在同一个
anything llm all right you could also
Anything LLM 实例上。
use chroma you could also use pine cone
您还可以使用 Chroma、Pine Cone、
you could also use hudon we8 all these
Hudon We8 等各种
different ones right here Astra DB and
不同的数据库，例如 Astra DB 和
then EMB better so anything llm also
EMB。Anything LLM 也
like I said has their own embedder so
像我之前提到的那样，拥有自己的嵌入器，因此可以
using their pre uh built-in embedding uh
使用其内置的嵌入提供程序，
provider or anything llm zero setup
或者 Anything LLM
required so these are really nice very
无需任何设置。这些功能非常
convenient that anything llm has these
实用，Anything LLM
built in all all local all private and
内置了所有这些功能，而且都是本地的、私有的。
then of course you can do open AI Azure
当然，您还可以使用 OpenAI、Azure、
local AI LM Studio coh here um you know
Local AI、LM Studio 等
all these different ones right here if
各种不同的数据库。
you you want okay next is the text
接下来是文本
splitter and chunking so here I'm not
分割和分块，这里我就不赘述了。 简单
going to go over what that is it's to do
来说，这
with the rag side of things um you know
跟文本处理有关，
search that up if you don't know what
如果你不知道这是什么，可以搜索一下。
that is but you can change the settings
你可以在
for that here text Chunk size as well as
这里更改文本块大小和
text Chunk overlap and you can see a
文本块重叠的设置，
description of each here too that should
这里也提供了每个设置的说明，应该对
help you out also too if you don't know
你有帮助。如果你不知道
what any of these settings are check out
这些设置是什么，请查看
the docs I'll leave those in the
文档，我会在
description down below and I'll go over
下面的说明中列出，稍后我会讲解
some of that in just a second Now voice
一些内容。现在来说说语音
and speech so you can change the speech
和语音处理，你可以更改语音
to text preference so you can choose the
转文本的偏好设置，选择
provider right here so local whisper
提供商。本地 Whisper
runs a whisper model locally on device
会在设备本地运行 Whisper 模型，
you can select the model right here
你可以选择模型，默认
which is this one by default and then
是这个。然后是语音
text the speech preference right here
偏好设置，
you could see the system native one so
你可以看到系统原生语音，也就是
using the built-in TTS uh service if
使用内置的 TTS 服务（如果
supported open AI 11 Labs you can even
支持 OpenAI Labs）。你甚至可以
use um Piper
使用 Piper
TTS okay a bunch of different stuff you
TTS，还有很多其他选择，你
could use open AI uh API compatible ones
可以使用 OpenAI API 兼容的 TTS，
as well and then transcript right here
以及这里提供的转录功能。OpenAI 就是其中之一，
here so open AI right here or anything
或者任何
llm built in one now using the local
内置的 TTS 服务。 在内存或 CPU
whisper model on machines with limited
有限的机器上，本地 Whisper 模型
Ram or CPU can install anything llm when
可以安装任何 llm。
processing media files we recommend at
处理媒体文件时，我们建议
least 2 GB of RAM and uploads uh files
至少 2 GB 内存，并上传
of 10 megabytes uh or more um the
10 MB 或更大的文件。
built-in model will automatically
内置模型会
download on the first use 250 megabytes
在首次使用时自动下载 250 MB。
okay and then admin settings so we have
接下来是管理员设置。
General admin settings right here so
这里有常规管理员设置，
enable network discovery we have
启用网络发现。
workspace chats right here so you can
这里有工作区聊天记录，您可以
see all the different workspace chats we
查看所有不同的工作区聊天记录。
go ahead delete some if need be you
如有需要，我们可以删除一些。您
you could clear chats export chats and
可以在这里微调模型，清除聊天记录，导出聊天记录（
CSV Json all these other ones right here
CSV、JSON 等格式）。还有
and then agent skills so this is where
代理技能。
you can enable or disable certain agent
您可以在这里启用或禁用某些代理
skills so by default these three right
技能。默认情况下，
here are enabled such as Rag and
这里启用了三个技能，例如 RAG 和
long-term memory so this is where you
长期记忆。您
can use rag for your AI agents like I
可以在这里为 AI 代理使用 RAG。例如，我
could upload a document or PDF whatever
可以上传一个文档或 PDF 文件，
using the agent and then I could also
然后使用代理询问有关该文档的问题。我还可以
say you know if it I ask it a specific
说，如果我询问它
question about a document like let's say
有关某个文档（例如
a book or something and then it gives me
一本书）的特定问题，它会
retrieves that answer for it I could say
检索该文档。 对此，我可以说“
hey remember this and then it would
嘿，记住这个”，然后它会将
store it in its long-term memory and
这个数据存储在长期记忆中。
then if I go to a new session where I
如果我进入一个新的会话，而我
didn't upload that document it would
没有上传过该文档，它
actually remember that right so that's
实际上会记住这一点，对吧？这
pretty cool and then View and summarize
很酷。接下来是“查看和摘要
documents so that one's enabled by
文档”，这个功能默认启用。
default and then scrape websites right
然后是“抓取网站”，
here so allow the agent to view and
允许代理查看和
scrape content on websites next is
抓取网站上的内容。接下来是“
generate and save files to browser um
生成文件并保存到浏览器”，也就是“
generate charts okay so some models
生成图表”。好的，有些模型与“
don't work as well with this generate
生成图表”功能配合使用效果不佳。还有“
charts web search so live web searching
网络搜索”，也就是实时网络搜索
and browsing so here you can enable uh
和浏览。在这里，您可以启用
you know different ones like Google
不同的搜索引擎，例如谷歌
search engine allows 100 queries a day
搜索引擎，它每天允许 100 次查询，
so it's free you can go to this link
是免费的。您可以访问这个链接进行
right here set it up you can get your
设置，您可以在这里获取您的
search engine ID as well as your program
搜索引擎 ID、程序
access API key right here and just put
访问 API 密钥，然后将
those in there there you could also use
它们输入到这里。您还
um the search API right here you could
可以使用搜索 API，例如
use Ser serper dodev you could use Bing
Ser、Serper、Dodev、Bing、
search surley search NG you could use
Surley Search、Google Search NG 等等，有
tavali a bunch of different options
很多不同的选项。
there and a lot of those do also have
还有一些
free um plans or give you like a free uh
免费的套餐，或者赠送
amount of tokens that you can use so you
一定数量的免费代币，您可以
can go ahead and use those as well and
利用这些代币。
then SQL connector so you can actually
然后是 SQL 连接器，您可以
connect to a specific SQL database and
连接到特定的 SQL 数据库，
then use your agent to um basically ask
然后使用您的代理来询问
question questions regarding the SQL
有关 SQL
connection right here so we can use post
连接的问题。例如，我们可以使用
grass MySQL SQL Server right here could
Postgrass MySQL SQL Server，您可以在这里
fill in the all the information right
填写
here about our database and then save
有关数据库的所有信息，然后保存
the connection I'm not going to do that
连接。我
right now now you can also create custom
现在不会这样做。您还可以创建自定义
skills so you would have to import these
技能，您需要导入这些技能。
llm agent docs surrounding this if you
如果您想创建自定义代理技能，可以查看 Anything LLM Agent 的相关文档。
I'm not going to cover that right now
我现在不会介绍这部分内容。
and then customization so you can change
然后是自定义功能，您可以更改
some stuff uh just regarding the
一些内容，例如
language to display um some stuff around
显示语言、外观、
the appearance some custom messages you
自定义消息（例如，您
can change new system message or new
可以更改新系统消息或新
user message and then you have different
用户消息）。此外，还有一些不同的
tools so event logs right here you can
工具，例如事件日志（您可以在这里
check these out developer API so you can
查看）、开发者 API（您可以
generate a new API key like so um and
生成新的 API 密钥）和
then browser extension so you can
浏览器扩展（您可以
generate a new browser API key and you
生成新的浏览器 API 密钥）。您
can go ahead check out the docs read
可以查看相关文档。 阅读
more about the browser API the docker uh
更多关于浏览器 API、Docker
developer API and you could check out
开发者 API 的信息，你也可以查看
their GitHub and check out those
他们的 GitHub 仓库，看看那些
extensions as well the browser uh
扩展程序，比如浏览器
extension and all that good stuff okay
扩展等等。好了，
now that we went over the main system
现在我们已经了解了主要的系统
settings let's go ahead and just like
设置，接下来让我们
test out a new workspace so if I go here
测试一下新的工作区。如果我在这里
type in the workspace name save now if I
输入工作区名称并保存，如果我
click on the workspace settings you can
点击工作区设置，你会
see like I said the settings here you
看到我刚才提到的设置，你
could go change some of these if need be
可以根据需要更改其中一些。
I'm just going to select this right here
我选择这里，
I'll select this update workspace um
选择“更新工作区”。
actually I could have just kept it the
实际上，我可以保持
same since we already have open AI as
原样，因为我们已经将 OpenAI 设置为
our default um llm let's go ahead into
默认工作区了。好了，我们进入
uh a thread right here so first off you
线程。首先，你
could go ahead and just like talk to it
可以和它对话。
right so here I said hi and now we're
我在这里说了“你好”，现在我们正在
just getting streamed from open AI um
接收来自 OpenAI 的流式传输，这里是
just some basic text right here now if
一些基本的文本。现在，如果
we go ahead and click on this is going
我们点击这里，就可以
to allow us to upload different things
上传不同的内容
to our rag so what can we upload for
到我们的工作区。我们可以上传什么呢？我们先来
uploading a document all right so I'm
上传一个文档。好的，我来上传。 我要把
going to upload this document on agent q
这份文档上传到 Agent Q
and agent e and I'm going to open that
和 Agent E 上，我打开后
you'll see both these documents are now
你会看到这两份文档正在
uploading right here so these are
上传。这些
documents on different videos I actually
文档是我之前用
did on these specific tools okay so this
这些工具制作的不同视频里的。好的，这份文档有点
one had an issue we'll just ignore that
问题，我们先忽略它，暂时只
we'll just keep agent Q for now um I
保留 Agent Q。嗯，我
could probably re-upload it but you'll
可能可以重新上传，但你会
see here agent Q is now in here if I
看到 Agent Q 现在就在这里。如果我
click on agent Q I want to right here
点击 Agent Q，在
you'll on the right you'll see our
右边你会看到我们的
stride workspace so this over here is on
Stride 工作区。这里显示的是
our document so if you want to add a
我们的文档。如果你想添加
bunch of different like we add some
很多不同的文档，比如把一些
similar documents to other workspaces we
类似的文档添加到其他工作区，我们
could do so or have you know only
可以这样做；或者你也可以只
specific documents in a specific
在特定的工作区添加特定的文档。
this allows it to make it very easy to
这样管理起来就非常方便了。
manage and then we can click on move to
然后我们可以点击“移动到
workspace as you'll see it's moved over
工作区”，你会看到它已经移动
to our workspace and then we can click
到我们的工作区了。然后我们可以点击“
save and embed and this is going to
保存并嵌入”，这会
actually update the workspace and embed
更新工作区并将
this document into our um Vector store
这份文档嵌入到我们的矢量存储中。好的，
right here all right as you can see
你可以看到
workspace updated successfully now we
工作区已成功更新，现在
have that document within our workspace
我们的工作区里就有这份文档了。太好了！
okay so that's great um now we can also
现在我们也可以
go ahead and use the buil-in scraper
使用内置的爬虫了。
right here so if I go
如果我输入
https and then R agents.com all right
https，然后输入 R agents.com，好的，
you'll actually already see that I have
你会看到我
this already let me just delete this and
已经有这个了。我把它删掉，
then we can just run this again so fetch
然后我们可以再运行一次。输入 fetch
website you can do this for any website
website，你可以对任何网站执行此操作，
and it is going to scrape it and link
它会抓取网站内容，链接
uploaded successfully so now I can go
上传成功。现在我可以
ahead and click on this and move it to
点击它，把它移动到
workspace I'm not going to embed it yet
工作区。我暂时不嵌入它，
because we're going to do a couple more
因为我们还要做一些其他的
things um so yeah you can create new
事情。你可以在这里创建新
folders here organize your documents
文件夹，整理你的文档，这非常
which is really nice can upload all
方便。你可以上传
these different types of documents audio
各种类型的文档，比如音频
files spreadsheet
文件、电子表格等等。你
and you can also go to data connectors
还可以访问数据连接器，
right here so this is really cool
这很棒，
because we can do things like connected
因为我们可以连接
GitHub repo if want if we want right so
GitHub 仓库（如果需要的话）。
you can enter in the credentials right
你可以在这里输入凭据：
here the access token the URL the branch
访问令牌、URL、分支（
if there's any files to ignore um you
如果有需要忽略的文件）。你还
can do get git lab
可以使用
repo bulk link scraper right here so
批量链接抓取工具，
this is really cool too you could you
这也很实用。你可以批量
know scrape um links in bulk right and
抓取链接，还可以
change some of the settings here um you
更改一些设置。 你
know Confluence right here and then
知道，这里有 Confluence，这里还有
YouTube transcript uh scraper right here
YouTube 文字稿抓取器。
so if I go ahead and go to my YouTube
假设我打开我的 YouTube
channel and grab a specific YouTube
频道，找到一个特定的 YouTube
video URL let's say I grab one of the
视频 URL，比如说我找到
videos I made yester a few days ago I'm
几天前做的一个视频，我会把 URL
going to paste this right here and then
粘贴到这里，然后使用“
collect transcript this is the one I did
收集文字稿”功能。这就是我之前
on screenshot to code you'll see here
在“截图转代码”里做的。你会看到“
screenshot to code has successfully been
截图转代码”功能已经成功抓取了文字
um scraped and we can go ahead and we
稿。我们继续，可以
will see that we got screenshot to code
看到“截图转代码”就在这里。现在
right here so I can go ahead move to
我可以把它移到
workspace and let me just remove this
工作区，然后把它
one to workspace so now we have these
从工作区移除。现在我们有了
two new ones right here that we're going
两个新的文档，我们要把它们
to actually embed let's save that and if
嵌入进去。保存一下。如果
everything goes well both of those yep
一切顺利，这两个文档都会嵌入进去。
so now we have three different documents
现在我们
embedded into our workspace all right
的工作区里嵌入了三个不同的文档。
you could remove documents from
你可以从工作区移除文档，也可以把
workspace you could pin documents to
文档固定到
workspace and that's pretty much it
工作区。
regarding documents okay now that we
关于文档的部分就这些了。好了，现在我们
have some documents in our workspace I
的工作区里有一些文档了，我
go ahead and start chatting with this
来和它对话，
and ask it specific questions regarding
问一些关于这些文档的具体问题。
them it should be able to pull those uh
它应该能够找到
answers so I just asked it what is agent
答案。所以我问了它“什么是代理
Q now it's giving us you know agent Q is
Q”，现在它正在回答。 你知道，Agent Q 是
an advanced AI system designed for
一个先进的人工智能系统，专为
autonomous web navigation blah blah blah
自主网页导航而设计，等等等等。
blah blah and we can actually click on
我们可以点击“
show citations and we we see that the
显示引用”，看到
citation is right here if I click on
引用就在这里。如果我点击
that citation we'll actually see where
这个引用，就能看到
it's we can see referenced for times we
它的位置，可以看到它的引用次数，
can see all the different information
可以看到所有
regarding what it you know used and
关于它用途的信息等等。非常
whatnot so pretty cool stuff if I go
酷！如果我
ahead exit this we could ask it another
退出这个界面，我们可以问它另一个
question we could say what stride agents
问题，比如“Stride Agents 是什么？”。好的，
all right now we can see stride agents
现在我们可以看到，Stride Agents
is a platform form that offers AI
是一个提供人工智能
powered Solutions designed to enhance
解决方案的平台，旨在增强
appointment booking blah blah blah blah
预约功能，等等等等。
blah we say what screenshot to code and
我们说“截图到代码”，
it should pull that information as well
它应该也能提取到这些信息，
show citations show citations and we can
显示引用，显示引用，我们可以
see all that information all right down
看到所有这些信息。好的，
here you have a few different options so
这里有几个不同的选项：
one you can attach different files to
一是你可以将不同的文件附加到
the chat two you can view available
聊天中；二是你可以查看可用的
slash commands for chatting so we got
聊天斜杠命令；还有“
like reset so clear your chat history
重置”，也就是清除聊天记录
and begin a new chat um we can change to
并开始新的聊天；我们可以更改
different text size from small to large
文本大小，从小到大
to normal we can speak uh speak our
再到正常；我们可以在
prompt right here so if I go ahead click
这里说出提示音。所以如果我
on this okay so now it should actually
好了，点击这里。现在应该可以正常
work okay so it actually just downloaded
工作了。
once you click that mic it's going to
点击麦克风图标后，它会
download The Whisper model and now we
下载 Whisper 模型。现在我们
can actually speak so if I click and I
可以说话了。如果我点击并
start typing or I'm starting to speak
开始输入文字，或者我现在开始说话，
right now and then I click stop now it
然后点击停止，它
should actually um upload our text right
应该会将我们说的话上传
here or what we spoke into the model all
到模型中。
right so as you can see here it
正如你在这里看到的，它
basically showed what we spoke right
显示了我们说的话，
here and it got a response of course
并且得到了回复。当然，
this isn't correct uh you know a correct
这并不正确，你需要一个正确的
prompt so I was just showcasing that now
提示。我只是在演示一下。还有
a few things too you can copy the
一些功能：你可以复制
response you can actually it seems like
回复；
you're DES use TTS right here you can
你可以使用文本转语音（TTS）功能；你可以
use um you can edit the response right
编辑回复；你可以
here you can generate a new response you
生成新的回复；你
could give a good like rate that as a
可以给这个
good response and you can also Fork the
回复点赞；你还可以创建
response so if I click on Fork it's
回复的分支。如果我点击“创建分支”，它会
thread from that specific response so
从这个回复创建一个新的对话分支。这样
you actually have two similar um
你就可以拥有两个类似的
conversations with the same contacts all
对话，联系人
the same information and that's useful
信息都相同，这也很有用。
as well all right next is this little at
接下来是这个小功能。
sign this is one of the things that
签名是
you're going to use a lot if you're
你在
using uh AI agents so we have here the
使用人工智能代理时会经常用到的东西之一。这里是
at agent um you know um at sign right
AT 代理，你知道，AT 签名就在这里。
here also keep note that it does say
还要注意，它说
custom agents are coming soon so this is
自定义代理即将推出，这
really cool because anything LM is
真的很棒，因为 Anything LM 一直在
constantly upgrading and improving their
不断升级和改进他们的
system which is really nice so if I
系统，这非常好。如果我
click on at agent now the at agent isn't
点击 AT 代理，AT 代理现在还没有被
uh invoked so swapping over into agent
调用，所以我们切换到代理
chat so now if like we configured a
聊天。现在，如果我们
different llm for our agent let's say
为代理配置了不同的 LLM，比如说，
then it would actually start using that
它就会开始使用该
llm all right so now we can actually ask
LLM。好的，现在我们可以让它
it to do something let's say recent open
做一些事情，比如查找最新的
AI news okay so now it should actually
OpenAI 新闻。好的，现在它应该会
use search in Google because that's what
在 Google 中搜索，因为
we put in we use the Google search and
我们输入的是 Google 搜索，
it's found 10 different results and it's
它找到了 10 个不同的结果，正在
looking over them and now it provided us
查看它们，现在它为我们提供了
four different updates so this is GPT 40
四个不同的更新。这是 GPT-40
update integration with Del okay so
更新与 Del 的集成。好的，
these are definitely not the best this
这些都是 Def。 这绝对不是最佳结果，这
is actually super old news so I'm
其实是条老新闻了，所以我打算
actually going to go ahead and try not
试试不用
using the Google method and see if I get
谷歌搜索，看看能不能得到
better results so I'm going to try
更好的结果。我把
changing the web search to serd right
网页搜索改成serd，就在
here let's click save just a test and
这里，我们点击保存，只是测试一下。
I'm going to search again recent open AI
我再搜索一下“OpenAI 最新
news and now it's using the serper dodev
新闻”，现在它用的是serper dodev
to search for uh open AI news and let's
来搜索“OpenAI 新闻”。
see so we got the news page right here
我们来看看，新闻页面在这里，是
we got the wired um okay so definitely
Wired的。嗯，好吧，这绝对
not the best uh as we can see here um
不是最佳结果。正如我们在这里看到的，它并
not pulling the most upto-date news
没有抓取到最新的新闻。
realistically it should be showing
实际上，它应该显示
things like uh search GPT etc etc it
像“搜索GPT”之类的结果。
looks like it's just you know pulling
看起来它只是抓取了
some of the top search results maybe I
一些热门搜索结果。也许我
could say you know what maybe it's
可以说，你知道吗？也许这
actually my prompt let's say recent open
实际上是我的提示，比如“OpenAI 最新
AI news he recent open AI News November
新闻”。“OpenAI 最新新闻
um 5th 2024 okay so this is actually
2024年11月5日”。好的，这才是真正的
definitely more recent open AI news um
OpenAI最新新闻。
so as you can see if I click here this
正如你所看到的，如果我点击这里，这
is a Reuters one November 5th 2024 so
是一条路透社的新闻，2024年11月5日。
definitely you know you want to be
当然，你需要
specific with the prompts um but yeah if
明确提示，嗯，如果
you do are specific with the prompts it
你明确提示，效果会非常
does work pretty pretty well all right
好。好的，
next I'm saying generate a chart of the
接下来，我要生成一张
recent open AI News November 2024 and we
2024 年 11 月 OpenAI 新闻的图表。我们
can see here it's rendering a pie chart
可以看到，它在这里渲染了一个饼图，
right here and we can see the different
可以看到不同的
um open AI news right so you know
OpenAI 新闻。当然，
definitely not something I would
我并不一定会
actually use necessarily like for open
用它来查看
AI news but I was just trying to use the
OpenAI 新闻，但我只是想用
open AI or the agent chart just to show
OpenAI 或 Agent 图表来
case what that is and how that works and
展示它是什么以及它是如何工作的，
it did it correctly now I'm going to say
它做得很好。现在我要让它
summarize the agent Q document all right
总结 Agent Q 的文档。好的，它正在
so it's looking for the available
查找可用文档，找到了
documents found three documents looking
三个文档，正在查找可用文档，找到了三个文档，并
grabbing all the context for agent q and
抓取了 Agent Q 的所有上下文。
now it summarized the documents purpose
现在它总结了文档：目的、
Technologies performance applications
技术、性能、应用、
Innovation features challenges and
创新、功能、挑战、
future work and more there we go it
未来工作等等。好了，它已经基本
pretty much summarized it now of course
总结好了。当然，
you could go ahead play around with some
你可以继续尝试一些
of the different other agent
其他的 Agent
capabilities and features and tools and
功能、特性和工具，就
like they said they are adding more and
像他们说的，他们正在添加更多功能，
you can also add custom ones so that's
你也可以添加自定义功能，这
pretty cool I am really excited to see
很棒，我真的很期待看到它
how anything llm continues to improve
如何运作。  LLM 一直在改进
its tool and I know a lot of you guys
它的工具，我知道你们很多人都
really love using olama or LM Studio or
喜欢使用 Olama、LM Studio 或
local models so I think this is really
本地模型，所以我认为它在
good for that as well as using a nice a
这方面真的很好用，而且还提供了一个很棒的
private chat interface especially well
私聊界面，尤其适合
you know if you're using local models of
使用本地模型的人。
course if you're not using close Source
当然，如果你不使用本地模型，
models but a private chat guey that
私聊界面就更方便了。它
allows you to easily build agents build
能让你轻松创建代理，构建
rag have your agents have access to
角色，让你的代理访问各种
tools um in a nice interface that's very
工具，而且界面简洁易用，
very easy to set up but anyways let me
设置起来也非常简单。总之，请在
anything llm in the comments down below
下方评论区告诉我你对 LLM 的任何想法，无论
you use it already or are using another
你是否已经在使用它，或者你正在使用其他
tool you have a better tool that you
工具，或者你更
prefer over anything llm and if you guys
喜欢哪个工具。如果你
are new to this channel we upload videos
是第一次来到这个频道，我们
every single day on AI automation
每天都会上传关于人工智能自动化、市场
Marketing sales business growth so if
营销、销售和业务增长的视频。如果
you like that type of content and you
你喜欢这类内容，并且觉得这个视频对你有
got some value here make sure to like
帮助，请务必点赞、
the video comment down below and
评论并
subscribe to stay up to date with the
订阅，以便及时获取
daily uploads also too guys if you
每日更新。另外，如果你
haven't already joined our free
还没有加入我们的免费
community stri community.com our free
社区 stricommunity.com、我们的免费
Facebook group and Discord Channel I'll
Facebook 群组和 Discord 频道，我会在
leave a link down below and then for
下面留下链接。 对于
some of you that run a business and you
一些经营企业并
need help growing your business with
需要帮助拓展业务的朋友，例如市场营销、
Marketing sales operations outbound
销售运营、外
prospecting paid ads or even
呼开发、付费广告，甚至需要
implementing AI agents like AI
将人工智能代理（例如人工智能
appointment Setters AI Co callers AI
预约员、人工智能客服专员、人工智能
textur or complete Ai call center
文本处理员或完整的人工智能呼叫中心
operation into your business to help you
运营）集成到您的业务中，以帮助您
accelerate your stride and scale and
加速发展并扩大规模，请访问
book a call down below at executive
executivestrive.com 预约通话，与
strive.com apply to speak to myself and
我和
my team and see if there's a potential
我的团队交流，看看是否
fit other than that guys I will see you
合适。除此之外，我们
in tomorrow's video keep hustling keep
明天视频见！继续努力奋斗，
grinding and of course guys accelerate
当然，祝各位加速发展，
your stride take care
保重！